Translated by Kizuna Sato
Translated by Ida
The sky of the starry sky
I'll give you a gift
To be able to dance
Make a dream
Of course I'll always be with you
If I could sing the song which you ask
I'll be happy
If you can't reach out to me
Let's not be busy with our hearts
We'll spend this very time together
And the movie we play is over
If you, if you, if you, if you
Do your thing, if I love you
I'll be on the path on the path towards you
Because I'm waiting for myself
It's all thanks to you, Muka-muka!
There are a lot of today!
Is this a new time machine?
Where is the wire?
I knew it would be easy for me to move, so I decided to come here.
I wanted to become a champion car-style as much as possible, so that I could be able to do it as much as possible.
I'm sure there are a lot of things to do, but I'm going to do it this time.
I'm going to do it this time.
Do you want to do it?
Are you going to do it like this?
Today, the weather forecast for the weather forecast was forecasted.
I'm going to do it this time.
Really?
Why do you need to do it like this?
It's a good question.
Actually, I have something important to do.
Something important?
I don't know.
There were a lot of times when I went to buy a car.
But the weather forecast was the same.
I thought about it at that time.
This is the opposite.
If you give me a chance, I'll give you a chance.
I'm not going to do it because I don't want to do it.
Right. I've made a mistake.
I see.
When I realized that I don't want to do it, I realized that I don't want to do it.
Where did you make this?
I made a special mistake.
I wonder why I can't do it because I don't want to do it.
I think that's what I'm going to do after that.
That's right.
That's what I'm going to do after that.
I made a special mistake.
What about you?
This time machine can also move well if you wear a hairpin.
That's right.
I see.
It's okay if you wear a hairpin.
That's why I'm going to do it now.
Oh, I made a mistake.
I wonder if it's a hairpin.
It's okay if you wear a hairpin.
Right.
Hey, don't you think you can do it because you have a hairpin?
Isn't that machine broken?
No, it's a hairpin.
If it was like this, I'd have to go to the hairpin before the plane.
It's bad, but I'm going to go home.
I'm going to have a new plan.
This is also a hairpin that I'm going to do.
Great.
I'm going to go home.
I'm going to have a new plan that I'm going to do.
Uiba-chan, wait a little longer.
Can you bring me a new plan?
What?
If you have a hairpin that you don't have a hairpin,
you might need it because you have a new plan.
Is that okay?
What's wrong with you?
Sometimes you need building design at the time machine.
Don't worry about it.
If you love a cactus, it's fine.
If you bring me a new plan, it's fine.
Bring me a new plan.
Great.
Come in.
Uuugh.
You realize you don't think it's about the fruits.
What are you doing, Muka-muka?
This is Shijin Yukikami!
What is Shijin Yukikami?
It's still morning, Muka-muka!
Is this Shijin Yukikami?
That's why I said that!
It's because Kami-sama's arrival is over.
Kami-sama is being attacked by Makura-moto.
Muka-muka is the most important person in the world!
Is that a dream?
It's not a dream!
It's true!
What are you talking about?
It's a dream!
No!
There's nothing!
Muka-chan!
It's me!
What is it?
Muka-san!
It's a dream!
What are you saying?
I have Kami-sama!
Muka-muka-chan!
I'm coming!
Who are you?
It's not me!
What are you talking about?
It's a dream!
Muka-muka-chan!
What are you talking about?
I thought it was a dream!
Kami-nari?
Then, I'll see you again!
Muka-muka-muka-chan!
Muka-muka-chan!
Muka-muka-muka-muka!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Are you alive?
Where are you?
Muka-muka-muka-muka!
Are you okay?
Did you come here?
Yes.
It's not like you were born in Korea, right?
I was dead.
That was Kami-sama's death.
I don't need to tell you anything!
Ranka-san said it!
If so, there will be a lot on top of my head.
Muka-muka-muka-muka-muka-muka-muka!
I'm waiting for you.
What are you doing?
I think I came to the Zyraki forest.
What?
The Zyraki forest, where you lived, is that Muka-shin?
It's strange.
Can't you use this electric power?
It's not a water supply.
It's not enough for the birth.
What's going on?
I did it.
I can't wait!
It's not that hard. It's the last time I've done it.
The final machine is the last time!
Banger! Banger! Banger!
Huh? Is it the first time I've seen a real human?
It's true.
It's the same as the real one.
Hey, isn't that a house?
Huh?
It's true.
Hey, there's a person.
Hey, Lanka!
What is it?
There's a person in the lab.
Huh?
Oh, it's really a house!
What are you doing?
What's wrong?
It's so early.
It's not.
Huh?
What did you do?
Hey, everyone. What's wrong?
Yo, Yo-chan!
Huh?
Hey, what's this?
What's wrong?
Where did you go?
Huh?
What's wrong?
Hey, what's wrong?
What is it?
What in the world?!
This is crazy.
It's really crazy.
It's not what you want.
There's nothing like it.
It's a lie, Lankan.
I'm sorry.
You're doing it again.
Oh, no!
Ah!
I'll get you!
Where are you going?
Where are you?
Help!
I'm scared!
It's me!
Help!
I'm scared!
What?
What's happening?
What's going on?
I'm scared!
I'm not scared!
It's not a bad guy, I guess.
No, it's not a bad guy.
I'm interested.
But you're talking.
Oh, what's wrong?
Oh, it's okay, but if your brother doesn't get hurt,
it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
What are you looking for?
It's okay, it's okay.
What?
Is it a fish?
Yes, it's a fish.
It's a fish, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
It's a cute baby fish.
Where did you go when you were a kid?
What?
Isn't there a father?
It's not a big deal, but it's a baby fish.
That's why you're looking for it together.
I can't look for this house anymore.
Yes, it's a fish.
I can't move.
What a strange guy.
Hello.
Your brother is okay.
I don't know, but he's like a living.
It's a fish. It's a fish.
Fish!
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's get fish.
Fish!
What's this?
Where's the fish?
I don't know what I was worried about.
It's a fish.
That's cute, isn't it?
Don't cry.
We'll be looking for each other.
Really?
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy that I'm here.
Huh?
Where's the fish?
Yo-chan, my brother's panic.
Me too.
I don't know what it is, but I'll do my best.
Come on, everybody!
Let's look for each other together, baby!
Last one!
I'm waiting for him.
What's that?
Where's my brother?
Brother.
What?
Come on, brother.
Brother, come on.
Brother, come on!
Come on, brother!
Brother, come on, brother!
Where are you?
Here.
Come on, brother.
Come on.
There. There. There.
Look. Look.
What's wrong with Tanaka?
Looks like she got up again.
I'm not going anywhere.
Why are you trying to get on me?
You're so annoying!
What are you doing here?
I'm going to get a phone card if I don't forget it.
Don't say that!
I don't even have a phone card.
What about the phone card?
Did you buy it?
I'm sorry.
It was early in the morning.
I'm going to get a good one.
You're right.
You're going to get a good phone card, aren't you?
I'm going to get a good phone card, too.
You're going to get a good phone card, too.
What are you two doing?
Are you not going to get a good phone card?
I'm not that kind of person.
But I don't know where you're going.
I want to get a good phone card like you!
Kaneko...
What's wrong with you?
I'm not a good person.
Who's that?
Kaneko...
Is that you?
What are you two doing?
You're not going to get a good phone card, are you?
Kaneko...
Look!
It's not a good phone card!
Kaneko...
Hey!
Stop!
Don't do that!
What are you two doing?
Kaneko...
Nice shoot!
I'm not going to get a good phone card, are you?
I wonder if I'm going to get a good phone card.
Hey!
Look!
You're really good!
Good girl?
Why do you scare me!?
Look!
I'm getting a fine credit!
실패!
실패!!!
That was definitely right!
That sounds amazing, isn't it?
Let me go!
Aaahh!
I'm not in a hurry, Mr. Mookamuko!
Look!
I won't let you die!
You can't even fight!
It wasn't easy!
I won't let you go!
Mookamuko!
Hello, Mr. Mookamuko!
Mom, what are you doing?
little Mookamuko!
Mom!
I'm too nervous!
Mr. Mookamuko!
You can easily win now!
Go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Ah, no, no, no!
If you do that, your neck will be torn.
What?
How's it going?
Hey, are you still in a hurry?
Hey, hey!
If your neck is torn, your neck won't be able to eat anything!
If you do something and eat something,
Your stomach will be cracked.
Your stomach is so dry and so cute.
So much so much.
What should we do if we put the stone,
we'll have to put the stone.
We'll have to put the stone, we'll have to put the stone, we'll have to put the stone.
That's great.
If you don't have the stone, it's okay.
This is a tough one.
It's hard for me.
I don't think I'll be able to miss it.
Ya-da-da-da-da-da-da-da!
Motog we go!
Retreat!
Oh?
Marigold!
Keep it up, follow!
Good luck!
We can do it, Marigold!
Marigold...
Marigold?
Ppl!
Good luck baby!
I really did it!
I did it!
Eira, did you win?
Huh?
I see.
You're a friend of mine, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
I'm a friend of mine, too.
Well...
Ah, wait a minute.
What are you doing?
I have something I want to ask you to do!
Here it is!
Where is it?
We're...
Where are we going?
We're going to the kitchen.
Crap!
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
Baladis, come on, come on, come on, come on!
Eira, come on!
Someone, they will go, anyone will go!
Let's go to the bathroom, please!
In the end, those who have always been praying
I hear the times like they are here
The things I've been waiting for
Are all there are
None of them
What can't be done are all gone
Please subscribe to the channel!
The next Muka Muka Paradise is the Muka Muka and the Muka Muka.
Muka Muka and the Muka family are looking forward to Muka!